{
	"name": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary",
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-1",
			"front": "A young person age 12 to 18 years.",
			"back": "adolescent"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-2",
			"front": "A disorder in which cholesterol and calcium build up inside the walls of the blood vessels, forming plaque, which eventually leads to a partial or complete blockage of blood flow.",
			"back": "atherosclerosis"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-3",
			"front": "Injury caused by pressure to enclosed body surfaces, for example, from too much pressure in the lungs.",
			"back": "barotrauma"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-4",
			"front": "A type of reasoning in which a child looks for approval from peers and society.",
			"back": "conventional reasoning"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-5",
			"front": "A young adult age 19 to 40 years.",
			"back": "early adult"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-6",
			"front": "Areas where the neonate’s or infant’s skull has not fused together; usually disappear at approximately 18 months of age.",
			"back": "fontanelles"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-7",
			"front": "A young child age 1 month to 1 year.",
			"back": "infant"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-8",
			"front": "The average number of years a person can be expected to live.",
			"back": "life expectancy"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-9",
			"front": "An adult age 41 to 60 years.",
			"back": "middle adult"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-10",
			"front": "An infant reflex in which, when an infant is caught off guard, the infant opens his or her arms wide, spreads the fingers, and seems to grab at things.",
			"back": "Moro reflex"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-11",
			"front": "A newborn age birth to 1 month.",
			"back": "neonate"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-12",
			"front": "The basic filtering units in the kidneys.",
			"back": "nephrons"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-13",
			"front": "An adult age 61 years or older.",
			"back": "older adult"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-14",
			"front": "An infant reflex that occurs when something is placed in the infant’s palm; the infant grasps the object.",
			"back": "palmar grasp reflex"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-15",
			"front": "A type of reasoning in which a child bases decisions on his or her conscience.",
			"back": "postconventional reasoning"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-16",
			"front": "A type of reasoning in which a child acts almost purely to avoid punishment or to get what he or she wants.",
			"back": "preconventional reasoning"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-17",
			"front": "A child age 3 to 6 years.",
			"back": "preschooler"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-18",
			"front": "A person who is 6 to 12 years of age.",
			"back": "school age"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-19",
			"front": "An infant reflex in which the infant starts sucking when his or her lips are stroked.",
			"back": "sucking reflex"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-20",
			"front": "A child age 1 to 3 years.",
			"back": "toddler"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-07-tag-vocabulary-card-21",
			"front": "The stage of development from birth to approximately 18 months of age, during which infants gain trust in their parents or caregivers if their world is planned, organized, and routine.",
			"back": "trust versus mistrust"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-07",
		"label": "Chapter 7"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "vocabulary",
			"label": "Vocabulary"
		}
	]
}